flabbi.com 2012-09-19

# Flabbi

## Policy last revised on 04/09/2011

flabbi's privacy policy consists of 5 sections  
    **1\. Identifiable Information**  
    **2\. Security**  
    **3\. Legal action**  
    **4\. Use of cookies**  
    **5\. Links to other websites**  
    **6\. Controlling your personal information**  
This privacy policy establishes how flabbi Ltd. ("The Company") uses and protects any information that you confide to The Company when you make use of this website.  
The Company is committed to ensuring that your privacy is always protected, so rest assured that if we ask you to provide determined data by which you can be identified when using this website, it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.  
The Company may change this policy by updating this page from time to time. We recommend you to check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 25/06/2011.

## 1\. Identifiable Information

We may ask you to provide the following information:  
•Name and title  
•contact information including e-mail address  
•demographic information such as age, sex, photo, preferences and interests  
•other information relevant to customer surveys and/or choices  
_The information we gather, what do we do with it?_  
We request this information because we require it to be able to understand your needs and desires, to provide you with the best quality service every time you enter and use the website, and in particular for the following reasons:  
•Internal record keeping.  
•We may use the information to improve the products and services we provide.  
•We may periodically send promotional emails to the email address you provided about special offers, new products that might be of your interest or other information which we think you may find useful.  
•From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by e-mail, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customize and upgrade the website according to your needs and interests.

## 2\. Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure at all times. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure of the data recorded in our files, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect on the internet.

## 3\. Legal action

We may disclose information pursuant to subpoenas, court orders, or other requests (including criminal and civil matters) if we have a good faith belief that the response is required by law. This may include respecting requests from jurisdictions outside of the India where we have a good faith belief that the response is required by law under the local laws in that jurisdiction, apply to users from that jurisdiction, and are consistent with generally accepted international standards. We may also share information when we have a good faith belief it is necessary to prevent fraud or other illegal activity, to prevent imminent bodily harm, or to protect ourselves and you from people violating our Statement of Rights and Responsibilities. This may include sharing information with other companies, lawyers, courts or other government entities.

## 4\. Use of cookies

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.  
We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it your (our customer's) needs. We only use this information for the purpose of statistical analysis and after that all filed data is removed from the system.  
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better running website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie doesn’t give us access to your computer or any information about you in any way other than the data you decide to share with us.  
You can choose to accept or decline these cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept them, but you can often modify your browser settings to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

## 5\. Links to other websites

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website and your activity will be governed by that site’s privacy statement and its other policies. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should be cautious and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

## 6\. Controlling your personal information

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:  
•whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes  
•If you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at support@flabbi.com.  
We will not under any circumstances sell or distribute your personal information to third parties unless we have your previous permission or are required by law to do so. We may use that information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting, but only if you tell us that you agree for this to happen.  
You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to support@flabbi.com  
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly review and correct any information found to be incorrect.
